[{"question": "When does India celebrate Independence Day?", "options": ["A. 15th August", "B. 2nd October", "C. 26th January", "D. 4th July"], "answer": "A. 15th August", "Level": "Easy"}, {"question": "Nobel prize is awarded for which of the following disciplines?", "options": ["A. Literature, peace and economics", "B. Medicine or Physiology", "C. Chemistry and Physics", "D. All the above"], "answer": "D. All the above", "Level": "Easy"}, {"question": "What is the theme of Asia health conference 2019?", "options": ["A. Competitiveness of India Inc- India@60: Forging Ahead", "B. Competitiveness of India Inc- India@75: Forging Ahead", "C. Competitiveness of India Inc- India@80: Forging Ahead", "D. Competitiveness of India Inc- India@90: Forging Ahead"], "answer": "B. Competitiveness of India Inc- India@75: Forging Ahead", "Level": "Easy"}, {"question": "Which state has Introduced new kin technology?", "options": ["A. Assam", "B. Delhi", "C. Haryana", "D. Punjab"], "answer": "D. Punjab", "Level": "Hard"}, {"question": "Who has won pro Kabadi League this season?", "options": ["A. Dabang Delhi", "B. Bengal Warriors", "C. Puneri paltan", "D. U Mumba"], "answer": "B. Bengal Warriors", "Level": "Hard"}, {"question": "First private train in India run between which of the two cities?", "options": ["A. Delhi-Lucknow", "B. Delhi-Ahmedabad", "C. Both of the above route", "D. None of the above"], "answer": "A. Delhi-Lucknow", "Level": "Hard"}, {"question": "As per a latest report by Brand Finance 2019, which is the India's most valuable brand?", "options": ["A. Reliance", "B. Tata Group", "C. State Bank of India", "D. Flipkart"], "answer": "B. Tata Group", "Level": "Hard"}, {"question": "At the end of March 2019, what was the amount of India's external debt?", "options": ["A. US $ 540 billion", "B. US $ 543 billion", "C. US $ 547 billion", "D. US $ 541 billion"], "answer": "B. US $ 543 billion", "Level": "Medium"}, {"question": "'LIBRA' an alternative of existing cryptocurrency like bitcoin is being developed by?", "options": ["A. Facebook", "B. Google", "C. Microsoft", "D. None of the above"], "answer": "A. Facebook", "Level": "Medium"}, {"question": "In which year was Sports Authority of India established?", "options": ["A. 1952", "B. 1967", "C. 1993", "D. 1982"], "answer": "D. 1982", "Level": "Medium"}, {"question": "Headquater of International Olympic Committee is situated at?", "options": ["A. Athens", "B. Lausanne", "C. Dubai", "D. None of the above"], "answer": "B. Lausanne", "Level": "Medium"}, {"question": "'The Coalition Years' is the autobiography of?", "options": ["A. L.K Advani", "B. Pranab Mukherjee", "C. Atal Behari Vajpayee", "D. Sonia Gandhi"], "answer": "B. Pranab Mukherjee", "Level": "Easy"}, {"question": "Which Indian revolutionary leader is known as 'Bagha Jatin'?", "options": ["A. Jatindranath Mukherjee", "B. Jatindranath Bannerjee", "C. Jatindranath Das", "D. Jatindranath bose"], "answer": "A. Jatindranath Mukherjee", "Level": "Easy"}, {"question": "Garampani Sanctuary is locate in which of the following places?", "options": ["A. Junagarh, Gujarat", "B. Kohima, Nagaland", "C. Diphu, Assam", "D. Gangtok, Sikkim"], "answer": "C. Diphu, Assam", "Level": "Easy"}, {"question": "Entomology studies what?", "options": ["A. Behavior of human beings", "B. Insects", "C. The origin and history of technical and scientific terms", "D. The formation of rocks"], "answer": "B. Insects", "Level": "Easy"}, {"question": "Galileo was an astronomer who", "options": ["A. Developed the telescope", "B. Discovered four satellites of Jupiter", "C. discovered that the movement of pendulum produces a regular time measurement", "D. All the above"], "answer": "B. Discovered four satellites of Jupiter", "Level": "Easy"}, {"question": "Name Capital of Australia", "options": ["A. Sydney", "B. Canberra", "C. Melbourne", "D. Adilaide"], "answer": "B. Canberra"}, {"question": "which is the capital of india", "options": ["A DELHI", "  DELHI", "B.MUMBAI", "C.GOA"], "answer": "A"}, {"question": "who is the pm of india", "options": ["A.sonia gandhi", "B.narendrea modi", "C.susma swaraj", "D. rahul gandhi"], "answer": "B.narendra modi"}]